part two directions you will hear a
question or statement and three
responses spoken in English they will
not be printed in your textbook and will
be spoken only one time select the best
response to the question or statement
and mark the letter A B or C on your
answer
sheet now let's begin with question
number
seven number seven when is the safety
inspection this month
a Friday
morning B at the main Factory
floor C next month's
budget number eight excuse me can you
help me find my
seat a thanks but I'd rather stay
here B certainly please follow
me C how long would it take to
finish number nine would you like
anything from our dessert
menu a I'll just have some
coffee B the bakery doesn't open until
10:
C yes I'd like to see him in a black
suit
number 10 do you know any pharmacies
around
here a no we've never met
before B the doctor gave me this
prescription C there's one on Emerson
Street number 11 did you proofread the
manuscript from George Samson
a we don't have enough proof for
now B yes I made some corrections
too C yes George has published two
books number 12 isn't that your umbrella
in the
corner a mine was
broken B it's not raining outside
C the forecast will be on in 5
minutes number
13 what construction project are you
involved
in a we are building a recreation
center B I didn't read the
instructions C the projected budget is
$5
million
number
14 did you make it to the Valerie's
party last
night a sorry we didn't have enough
supplies B actually tomorrow is better
for me
c no the traffic was really
bad number 15 weren't you at the
International Job Fair last
month a yes were you
too B I was transferred to that
department C no the offering prices were
too
low number
16 where is the National Conference
being held this
year a from August 2nd through August
5th B to introduce a new line of
products C they're still considering
some
options number
17 the attendant was just here wasn't
he a I think the address was
wrong B no he left an hour ago
C yes it's just the right
size number
18 why didn't we order new printer for
the sales
team a we should make at least 20
copies B we could get the manager's
approval C the employees are getting
trainings
number
19 you went to the lecture didn't
you a you mean the one Mr Bean
gave
B yes put it over
here C the weather is
awesome number
20 why are the applications on Mr Kim's
desk
a he will apply for the
job B he wants to review them one more
time C the position needs much
experience number
21 do you know who's in charge of
recording the actual
performance a I think I
am B you could put it on your credit
card
C Maria Sanchez gave an excellent
speech number 22 how do you fill the
printer when it's out of
paper a it's temporarily out of
service B we should call the technician
right
away C it goes in the on the
bottom number
23 the fax machine isn't working
anymore a can you send it by faster
delivery B I thought it was fixed last
week C do you like working here so
far number 20 24 how many people are
expected to show up at the training
seminar a they are showing it every 2
hours B for the next 6 to 8
months C everyone from the sales
division number
25 would you like me to show you how to
set up the new accounting program
a thanks I'm having trouble with
it B the software has a good
reputation
C yes that's a great
team number
26 the apartment will be available in
July
a is it for sale or for
lease B they moved in
recently C I'll just take a small
part number 27 couldn't we reschedule
our meeting for
tomorrow a please bring your
briefcase B actually I'll be visiting
the Milan
office C how did the meeting go
number 28 would you like to go to the
cafeteria or do you want to go out for
lunch
a yes the lunch was
delicious B that place is known to be
famous C actually I brought some
sandwiches number
29 has Mr Wills been notified of the
promotion a we didn't know each other
then B I told him in person at the
morning
meeting
C yes we have updated the
program number
30 are you busy with your work now or
can you help me move these boxes
a I'll be done in a few
minutes B let's order some more supplies
today C the shipment got delayed at the
port number
31 we have introduced a new line of
women's wear this month haven't
we a next month is our 20th anniversary
B yes the introduction was brief but
efficient
C yes and we are expecting High
[Music]
sales now let's begin with question
number
seven number seven when is the safety
inspection this
month a Friday
morning B at the main Factory
floor C next month's
budget number eight excuse me can you
help me find my
seat a
thanks but I'd rather stay
here B certainly please follow
me
c how long would it take to
finish number nine would you like
anything from our dessert
menu a I'll just have some
coffee B the bakery doesn't open until
10:
C yes I'd like to see him in a black
suit number 10 do you know any
pharmacies around
here a no we've never met
before B the doctor gave me this
prescription C there's one on Emerson
Street
number 11 did you proofread the
manuscript from George
Samson a we don't have enough proof for
now B yes I made some corrections
too C yes George has published two
books number 12 isn't that your umbrella
in the
Corner a mine was
broken B it's not raining
outside
C the forecast will be on in 5
minutes number
13 what construction project are you
involved
in a we are building a recreation
center B I didn't read the
instructions C the projected budget is
$5
million number
14 did you make it to the Valerie's
party last
night a sorry we didn't have enough
supplies B actually tomorrow is better
for me
see no the traffic was really
bad number
15 weren't you at the International Job
Fair last
month a yes were you
too B I was transferred to that
department C no the offering prices were
too
low
number 16 where is the National
Conference being held this
year
a from August 2nd through August
5th B to introduce a new line of
products C they're still considering
some
options number
17 the attendant was just here wasn't he
a I think the address was
wrong B no he left an hour
ago
C yes it's just the right
size number
18 why didn't we order new printer for
the sales
team a we should make at least 20
copies B we could get the manager's
approval C the employees are getting
trainings number
19 you went to the lecture didn't
you a you mean the one Mr Bean
gave
B yes put it over
here see the weather is
awesome
number
20 why are the applications on Mr Kim's
desk a he will apply for the
job B he wants to review them one more
time C the position needs much
experience number
21 do you know who's in charge of
recording the actual
performance a I think I
am B you could put it on your credit
card
C Maria Sanchez gave an excellent
speech number 22 how do you fill the
printer when it's out of
paper a it's temporarily out of
service B we should call the technician
right
away C it goes in the drawer on the
bottom number
23 the fax machine isn't working
anymore a can you send it by faster
delivery B I thought it was fixed last
week C
do you like working here so
far number 24 how many people are
expected to show up at the training
seminar a they are showing it every 2
hours B for the next 6 to 8
months
C everyone from the sales
division
number
25 would you like me to show you how to
set up the new accounting
program a thanks I'm having trouble with
it B the software has a good
reputation
C yes that's a great
team number
26 the apartment will be available in
July
a is it for sale or for
lease B they moved in
recently C I'll just take a small
part number 27 couldn't we reschedule
our meeting for
tomorrow a please bring your
briefcase B actually I'll be visiting
the Milan
office C how did the meeting
go number 28 would you like to go to the
cafeteria or do you want to go out for
lunch
a yes the lunch was
delicious B that place is known to be
famous C
actually I brought some
sandwiches number
29 has Mr Wills been notified of the
promotion a we didn't know each other
then B I told him in person at the
morning
meeting see yes we have updated the
program
number
30 are you busy with your work now or
can you help me move these
boxes a I'll be done in a few
minutes B let's order some more supplies
today C the shipment got delayed at the
port number
31 we have introduced a new line of
women's wear this month haven't
we a next month is our 20th
anniversary B yes the introduction was
brief but
efficient
C yes and we are expecting High
sales
all